<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on @tomkealey</title>
    <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on @tomkealey</description>
    <image>
      <title>@tomkealey</title>
      <url>https://tomkealey.github.io/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Not the Critic Who Counts</title>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/not-the-critic-that-counts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/not-the-critic-that-counts/</guid>
      <description>The Man in the Arena It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong
man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better.
The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is
marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who
comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudyard Kipling</title>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/if/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/if/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll confess that poetry has rarely commanded a high position in my reading stack, yet somehow If by Rudyard Kipling has defied the algorithm odds and struck a chord with my inner stoic.
If If you can keep your head when all about you
Are losing theirs and blaming it on you,
If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you,
But make allowance for their doubting too; If you can wait and not be tired by waiting,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Player</title>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/football-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/football-player/</guid>
      <description>Taking inspiration from Football Management to guide reflections on player performance, potential, impact and development as an Engineering Manager.
Focus Areas:
1. Current Performance 2. Future Potential 3. Overall Impact 4. Personal Development Current Performance Technical Skills How proficient are you in ball control, passing, shooting, and defensive skills? What is your accuracy and consistency in executing these technical aspects in matches? Tactical Awareness How well do you understand and implement team strategies during matches?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager</title>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/football-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/football-manager/</guid>
      <description>Taking inspiration from Football Management to guide reflections on my performance, potential, impact and development as an Engineering Manager.
Focus Areas:
1. Current Performance 2. Future Potential 3. Overall Impact 4. Personal Development Current Performance Team Performance Assess the overall performance of your team in recent matches. Reflect on key victories, draws, and losses, and identify patterns or trends. Player Development Evaluate the individual development and performance of key players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello Hugo</title>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/hello-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/hello-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In search of a platform for this blog, I stumbled upon Hugo and got cosy with Static Site Generators. Hugo promised a fast and modern static site generator written in Go, designed to make website creation fun again. The inner geek in me was excited by that and the secret nerdy joy of writing posts in Markdown and pushing them to Github Pages to build and deploy appealed to me.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
