<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on @tomkealey</title>
    <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on @tomkealey</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://tomkealey.github.io/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gorilla Retro</title>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/gorilla-retro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/gorilla-retro/</guid>
      <description>Some iterations have natural drama, surprises or tension to mine, while others are dull by comparison. Even the most dedicated and high-performing teams can struggle to rise to the occasion on their 89th retro together. Managers are not immune.
We have experimented with frameworks yet found themes to be a favoured catalyst for creativity. The light constraint offers a lens through which to view the past and focus the mind, while sparking creative juices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retro Thursday</title>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/retro-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/retro-thursday/</guid>
      <description>Until lately, we would wrap up an iteration with a demo and a retro. It seemed the logical thing to do and we&amp;rsquo;d been doing it that way for ages.
Rules are made to be broken. Now, we hold the retro on the penultimate day of the iteration. And while there&amp;rsquo;s no reduction in the number of meetings, the run in to the finish feels gentler and the retro feels fresher which is perfect for a creative space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomkealey.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>In search of a platform for this blog, I stumbled upon Hugo and got cosy with Static Site Generators. Hugo proomised a fast and modern static site generator written in Go, designed to make website creation fun again. The inner geek in me was excited by that and the secret nerdy joy of writing posts in Markdown and pushing them to Github Pages to build and deploy appealed to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
